Guide to the E. L. Doctorow Papers 1931-2016 MSS.056
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XVI. Printed Material
  - Nabokov, Vladimir. Invitation to a Beheading. Greenwich: Fawcett Publications., 1960 (Box 103)
  - Wilson, Angus (ed.). The Portable Dickens. New York: Penguin Books., 1983 (Box 103)
  - A Thumbnail History of Mexico., 1990 (Box 103)
  - Avignone, June. On Going Home Again. Synthetic City., 2001 (Box 103)
  - Shakespeare, William. Hamlet. New York: Penguin Books., 1980 (Box 103)
  - Chaucer, Geoffrey. The Canterbury Tales. New York: Penguin Books., 1977 (Box 103)
  - Friedrich, Otto. Before the Deluge. New York: Avon Books., 1972 (Box 103)
  - Mason, J. Alden. The Ancient Civilizations of Peru. New York: Penguin Books., 1979 (Box 103)
  - Elkann, Alain. Piazza Carignano. Boston: The Atlantic Monthly Press., 1985 (Box 103)
  - Cook, Karin. What Girls Learn. New York: Pantheon Books., 1997 (Box 103)
  - Rossi, Agnes. The Quick: A Novella and Stories. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1992 (Box 103)
  - Bass, Rick. The Watch Stories. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1989 (Box 103)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis. Kidnapped. New York: Airmont Books., 1963 (Box 103)
  - Defoe, Daniel. The Journal of the Plague Year. New York: Penguin Books., 1966 (Box 103)
  - Marlowe, Christopher. Doctor Faustus. New York: New American Library., 1969 (Box 103)
  - Wilbur, Richard (ed.). Seventeenth Century English Minor Poets. New York: Dell Publishing., 1964 (Box 103)
  - Yale English/ Spanish Conversation Guide., 1972 (Box 103)
  - Dodd, C.H. The Founder of Christianity. New York: Macmillan Publishing Company., 1970 (Box 103)
  - Orwell, George. Burmese Days. New York: Signet Classic., 1963 (Box 103)
  - Calder, Ritchie. Medicine and Man. New York: Mentor Books., 1963 (Box 103)
  - Scranton, Roy and Matt Gallagher (ed.). Fire and Forget. Boston: Da Capo Press., 2012 (Box 104)
  - Phillips, Louis. The Woman who Wrote "King Lear". New York: Pleasure Boat Studio., 2009 (Box 104)
  - Helmreich, William B. The New York Nobody Knows: Walking 6000 Miles in the City. Princeton: Princeton University Press., 2013 (Box 104)
  - Murphy, Yannick. Signed, Mata Hari. New York: Little, Brown and Co., 2007 (Box 104)
  - Healy, Tom. What The Right Hand Knows. New York: Four Way Books., 2009 (Box 104)
  - The Joint WGA/ Industry Committee on the Professional Status of Writers. Guidelines for Writers, Producers, and Executives int he Making of Feature Films and Long-Form Television., 1993 (Box 104)
  - Gilmore, Jennifer. Something Red., 2011 (Box 104)
  - Eeman, Carl. Encampment. Round Lake: Melange Press., 2009 (Box 104)
  - Von Der Lippe, Angela. The Truth About Lou. New York: Perseus Books., 2006 (Box 104)
  - Klima, Ivan. My Crazy Century. New York: Grove Press., 2010 (Box 104)
  - Trigoboff, Joseph. The Shooting Gallery. Guilford: The Lyons Press., 2002 (Box 104)
  - Houghton, Norris (ed.). Great Russian Short Stories. New York: Dell Publishing., 1958 (Box 104)
  - Shibutani, Tamotsu. Improvised News. Indianapolis: The Bobbs-Merrill Company., 1966 (Box 104)
  - Ackerman, Diane. On Extended Wings. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons., 1987 (Box 104)
  - Hunter, Kathryn Montgomery. Doctors' Stories. Princeton: Princeton University Press., 1991 (Box 104)
  - Egan, Robert and Kurt Pitzer. Eating with the Enemy. New York: St. Martin's Press., 2010 (Box 104)
  - Bradley, Peter. This Book is Full of Carp. Saint Paul: Hungry Mind Press., 1997 (Box 105)
  - Sebald, W.G. and Jan Peter Tripp. Unrecounted. New York: New Directions Books., 2004 (Box 105)
  - Paley, Grace. Enormous Changes at the Last Minute. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1973 (Box 105)
  - Thomson, Richard. Edgar Degas: Waiting. Malibu: J. Paul Getty Museum., 1995 (Box 105)
  - Leighton, Maxinne Rhea. An Ellis Island Christmas. New York: Penguin Books., 1992 (Box 105)
  - Wallace, Jim. Terror on the Titanic. New York: Bantam Books., 1996 (Box 105)
  - Hage, Rawi. De Niro's Game. New York: Harper Perennial., 2006 (Box 105)
  - Abraham, Pearl. The Seventh Beggar. New York: Riverhead Books., 2005 (Box 105)
  - Dillard, Annie. The Annie Dillard Reader. New York: Harper Perennial., 1994 (Box 105)
  - Dillard, Annie. The Writing Life. New York: Harper Perennial., 1990 (Box 105)
  - Center for Constitutional Rights. Docket. Fall 1995. New York. (Box 105)
  - Pizer, Donald (ed.). Jack London: Novels and Social Writings. New York: Literary Classics of the United States., 1982 (Box 105)
  - Howard, Richard (ed.). Henry James: Collected Travel Writings, The Continent. New York: Literary Classics of the United States., 1993 (Box 105)
  - Lasch, Christopher. The Culture of Narcissism. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1978 (Box 105)
  - Aitken, Robert. Taking the Path of Zen. San Francisco: North Point Press., 1982 (Box 105)
  - Postman, Neil. Technopoly. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1992 (Box 105)
  - Dreiser, Theodore. Sister Carrie. Philadephia: University of Pennsylvania Press., 1981 (Box 105)
  - Jingsheng, Wei. The Courage to Stand Alone. New York: Penguin Books., 1996 (Box 105)
  - Abraham, Peal. Giving Up America. New York: Riverhead Books., 1998 (Box 105)
  - Schama, Simon. Citizens: A Chronicle of the French Revolution. New York: Vintage Books., 1989 (Box 106)
  - Wilson, Robert A. (ed). Character Above All. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1995 (Box 106)
  - Meyer, Michael (ed.). The Bedford Introduction to Literature. Boston: Bedford St. Martin's., 1996 (Box 106)
  - Rushdie, Salman. The Satanic Verses. New York: Viking Press., 1989 (Box 106)
  - Whelan, Richard. Drawing the Line. Boston: Little, Brown and Co., 1990 (Box 106)
  - McNeillie, Andrew (ed.). The Essays of Virginia Woolf. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich., 1987 (Box 106)
  - Dostoevsky, Fyodor. Crime and Punishment. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1992 (Box 106)
  - Strassler, Robert B. (ed.). The Landmark Thucydides. New York: The Free Press., 1996 (Box 106)
  - Frye, Northrop. Words with Power. New York: Harcourt Brace Jovanovich, Publishers., 1990 (Box 107)
  - Woodward, W.E. The Way our People Lived. New York: American Book-Stratford Press, Inc., 1944 (Box 107)
  - Rose, Steven. The Conscious Brain. New York: Random House., 1976 (Box 107)
  - McNamara, John. History in Asphalt. Bronx: The Bronx County Historical Society., 1984 (Box 107)
  - Perec, Georges. W or The Memory of Childhood. Boston: David R. Godine., 1988 (Box 107)
  - Levitas, G.B. (ed.). The World of Psychology. New York: George Braziller., 1963 (Box 107)
  - Forche, Carolyn. Against Forgetting. New York: W.W. Norton and Co., 1993 (Box 107)
  - Carroll, Peter N. The Odyssey of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade. Stanford: Stanford University Press., 1994 (Box 107)
  - Dee, Jonathan. St. Famous. New York: Doubleday., 1996 (Box 107)
  - Harris, Marvin. Cannibals and Kings. New York: Random House., 1977 (Box 107)
  - Gardels, Nathan P. At Century's End. La Jolla: ALTI Publishing., 1994 (Box 107)
  - Kessner, Thomas. Capital City. New York: Simon and Schuster., 2003 (Box 107)
  - Maraniss, David. The Clinton Enigma. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1998 (Box 108)
  - Lasch, Christopher. The Minimal Self. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1984 (Box 108)
  - Malraux, Andre. Man's Fate. New York: Vintage Books., 1968 (Box 108)
  - Gide, Andre. The Immoralist. New York: Bantam Books., 1969 (Box 108)
  - Howe, Irving. Revolution at Berkeley. New York: The Dial Press., 1965 (Box 108)
  - Nozick, Robert. Philosophical Explanations. Cambridge: Harvard University Press., 1983 (Box 108)
  - Smith, Adam. The Wealth of Nations. New York: Modern Library., 1965 (Box 108)
  - Wyatt, Will. The Secret of the Sierra Madre. Garden City: Doubleday and Company., 1980 (Box 108)
  - Gould, Stephen Jay. Hen's Teeth and Horse's Toes. New York: W.W. Norton and Co., 1983 (Box 108)
  - Congdon, Don (ed.). The Thirties. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1962 (Box 108)
  - Henry, Jules. Jungle People. New York: Vintage Books., 1964 (Box 108)
  - Sacks, Sheldon. Fiction and the Shape of Belief. Berkeley: University of California Press., 1967 (Box 108)
  - Hawkins, Gerald S. Stonehenge Decoded. New York: Dell Publishing Co., 1965 (Box 108)
  - Thoreau, Henry David. Cape Cod. New York: Penguin Books., 1987 (Box 108)
  - Friedlander, Saul. When Memory Comes. New York: Avon Books., 1978 (Box 108)
  - Labor, Earle, Robert C. Leitz, I. Milo Shepard (eds.). The Letters of Jack London. Stanford: University of Stanford Press., 1988 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: A Republic Divided. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: The Executive Branch. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: The Legislative Branch. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: The Press. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: The Public Schools. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Annenberg Democracy Project. Institutions of American Democracy: The Judicial Branch. New York: Oxford University Press., 2007 (Box 109)
  - Mann, Thomas. Confession of Felix Krull, Confidence Man. New York: The New American Library., 1995 (Box 109)
  - Moody, Anne. Coming of Age in Mississippi. New York: Dell Publishing., 1968 (Box 109)
  - Warren, George. Gang Wars of the 30s. Chatsworth: Barclay House., 1974 (Box 109)
  - Wilson, Edmund. The Wound and the Bow. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1978 (Box 109)
  - Rhys, Jean. Sleep it Off, Lady. New York: Popular Library., 1978 (Box 109)
  - Lederer, Richard. Crazy English. New York: Pocket books., 1990 (Box 109)
  - Taylor, Peter. A Summons to Memphis. New York: Ballantine Books., 1986 (Box 112)
  - Taibo, Paco Ignacio. No Happy Ending. New York: Warner Books, Inc., 1993 (Box 112)
  - Schneider, Daniel E. The Psychoanalyst and the Artist. New York: A Mentor Book., 1962 (Box 112)
  - Kazin, Alfred. New York Jew. New York: Vintage Books., 1979 (Box 112)
  - Mountain, Marian. The Zen Environment. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1983 (Box 112)
  - Finley, M.I. (ed). The Portable Greek Historians: The Essenence of Herodotus, Thucydides, Xenophon, Polybius. New York: The Viking Press., 1959 (Box 112)
  - Goffman, Erving. The Presentation of Self in Everyday Life. New York: Doubleday Anchor Books., 1959 (Box 112)
  - Eisenberg, Deborah. Under the 82nd Airborne. New York: Ivy Books., 1992 (Box 112)
  - Kerouac, Jack. On the Road. New York: New American Library., 1957 (Box 112)
  - Souza, Marcio. The Emperor of the Amazon. New York: Avon Books., 1980 (Box 112)
  - Abu-Jamal, Mumia. Death Blossoms. Farmington: The Plough Publishing House., 1997 (Box 112)
  - Krevisky, Joseph and Jordan L. Linfield. The Bad Speller's Dictionary. New York: Random House., 1987 (Box 112)
  - Abu-Jamal, Mumia. Live from Death Row. Reading: Addison-Wesley Publishing Company., 1995 (Box 112)
  - West, Nathanael. Miss Lonelyhearts and the Day of the Locust.New York: New Directions Books., 1933 (Box 112)
  - Benjamin, Walter. Illuminations. New York: Schocken Books., 1968 (Box 112)
  - Valades, Adrian Garcia. Teotihuacan: The City of the Gods. Mexico: Ediciones Orto, S.A., 1981 (Box 112)
  - Phillips, Robert (ed). Aspects of Alice. New York: Vintage Books., 1971 (Box 112)
  - McPhee, Nancy. The Book of Insults: Ancient and Modern. London: Penguin Books., 1978 (Box 112)
  - Coover, Robert. Ghost Town: A Novel. New York: Henry Holt and Company., 1998 (Box 112)
  - Bentley, Eric (ed.). The Theory of the Modern Stage. London: Penguin Books., 1968 (Box 112)
  - Barnstone, Tony and Chou Ping (trans.). The Art of Writing: Teachings of the Chinese Masters. Boston: Shambhala., 1996 (Box 112)
  - Stone, Edward (ed.). Incident at Harper's Ferry. Englewood Cliffs: Prentice-Hall., 1958 (Box 112)
  - Benedict, Elizabeth. The Joy of Writing Sex: A Guide for Fiction Writers. Cincinnati: Story Press., 1996 (Box 112)
  - Woof, Virginia. Flush. New York: Harvest Books., 1983 (Box 114)
  - Callow Jr., Alexander B. The Tweed Ring. London: Oxford University Press., 1972 (Box 114)
  - Zencey, Eric. Panama. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux., 1995 (Box 114)
  - Blumenthal, Michael. Weinstock Among the Dying. Cambridge: Zoland Books., 1993 (Box 114)
  - Steinbock, Dan. Triumph and Erosion in the American Media and Entertainment Industries. Westport, Conn: Quorum Books., 1995 (Box 114)
  - Ginsberg, Allen. Kaddish and other Poems. San Francisco: City Lights Books., 1961 (Box 114)
  - Lelchuk, Alan. Playing the Game. Dallas: Baskerville Publishers Inc., 1995 (Box 114)
  - Terry, Marshall. Old Liberty. Lubbock, Tex: Texas Tech University Press., 1991 (Box 114)
  - Homes, A.M. In a Country of Mothers. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1993 (Box 114)
  - Hendrickson, Paul. The Living and the Dead. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1996 (Box 114)
  - Taylor, William R. (ed). Inventing Times Square. New York; Russel Sage Foundation., 1991 (Box 114)
  - Borovitz, Mark. The Holy Thief. New York: Harper Collins., 2004 (Box 114)
  - The Committee to Protect Journalists. Attacks on the Press in 1995. New York: The Committee to Protect Journalists. (Box 114)
  - Berger, John. Pig Earth. New York: Pantheon Books., 1979 (Box 114)
  - Iossel, Mikhail. Every Hunter Wants to Know. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1991 (Box 114)
  - Heschel, Abraham J. The Prophets. New York: Harper and Row, Publishers., 1962 (Box 115)
  - May, Ernest R and Philip D. Zelikow (eds). The Kennedy Tapes: Inside the White House During the Cuban Missile Crisis. Cambridge: The Belknap Press of Harvard University Press., 1997 (Box 115)
  - Rifkin, Jeremy. The European Dream. New York: Penguin Books., 2004 (Box 115)
  - Weisberg, Richard H. Vichy Law and the Holocaust in France. New York: New York University Press., 1996 (Box 115)
  - Milano, Paolo (ed). The Portable Dante. New York: The Viking Press., 1949 (Box 115)
  - Chilcote, Ronald H. and Joel C. Edelstein (eds). Latin America: The Struggle with Dependency and Beyond. New York: John Wiley and Sons., 1974 (Box 115)
  - Schmidt, Paul (trans). Arthur Rimbaud: Complete Works. New York: Harper Colophon Books., 1976 (Box 115)
  - Kessler, Milton. The Grand Concourse. Binhamton, NY: MSS., 1990 (Box 115)
  - Pennington, Anne (trans). VaskoPopa: Collected Poems 1943-1976. New York: Persea Books., 1978 (Box 115)
  - Greene, James (trans). Osip Mandelstam. Boulder: Shambhala., 1978 (Box 115)
  - Shawn, Wallace. The Fever. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1991 (Box 115)
  - Albee, Edward. Three Tall Women. New York: Penguin Books., 1995 (Box 115)
  - Eden, Emily. The Semi-Attached Couple and the Semi-Detached House. New York: The Dial Press., 1982 (Box 115)
  - Rude, George. The Crowd in History 1730-1848. London: Lawrence and Wishart., 1981 (Box 115)
  - Ratushinskaya, Irina. Poems. Ann Arbor, MI: Hermitage Books., 1984 (Box 115)
  - Epstein, Daniel Mark. The Boy in the Well and Other Poems. Woodstock: The Overlook Press., 1995 (Box 115)
  - Wright, James. To a Blossoming Pear Tree. New York: Farrar, Straus and Giroux., 1977 (Box 117)
  - Holldobler, Ber and Edward O. Wilson. Journey to the Ants: A Story of Scientific Exploration. Cambridge: The Belknap Press of Harvard University Press., 1994 (Box 117)
  - Terras, Victor. A History of Russian Literature. New Haven: Yale University Press., 1991 (Box 117)
  - Marx, Robert (ed). Famous American Plays of the 1980s. New York: Laurel Books., 1988 (Box 117)
  - Racine. Andromache and Other Plays. New York: Penguin Books., 1976 (Box 117)
  - Metraux, Guy S. and Francois Crouzet (eds). The Nineteenth-Century World. New York: Mentor Books., 1963 (Box 117)
  - Ziman, Larry, Madeline Sharples and Nicky Selditz (eds). The Great American Poetry Show: Volume 2. West Hollywood: The Muse Media., 2010 (Box 117)
  - Ziman, Larry, Madeline Sharples and Nicky Selditz (eds). The Great American Poetry Show: Volume 1. West Hollywood: The Muse Media., 2010 (Box 117)
  - Melville, Herman. Tales, Poems and other Writings. New York: The Modern Library., 2001 (Box 117)
  - Passos, John Dos. U.S.A. Boston: Houghton Mifflin., 1946 (Box 117)
  - Toole, John Kennedy. A Confederacy of Dunces. Baton Rouge: Louisiana State University Press., 1980 (Box 117)
  - Baker, Carlos. Ernest Hemingway: A Life Story. New York: Avon Books., 1969 (Box 117)
  - Weart, Spencer R. Nuclear Fear. Cambridge: Harvard University Press., 1988 (Box 117)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. We Were the Mulvaneys. New York: Penguin Books., 1996 (Box 118)
  - Cockburn, Leslie. Out of Control. New York: Atlantic Monthly Press., 1987 (Box 118)
  - Rubin, Harriet. Dante in Love. New York: Simon and Schuster., 2004 (Box 118)
  - Dolnick, Edward. Madness on the Couch. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1998 (Box 118)
  - Pells, Richard H. Radical Visions and American Dreams. New York: Harper and Row, Publishers., 1973 (Box 118)
  - Hertzberg, Arthur. The Jews in America. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1989 (Box 118)
  - Beschloss, Michael R. Taking Charge. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1997 (Box 118)
  - Wood, Trish. What WAs Asked of Us. New York: Little, Brown and Company., 2006 (Box 118)
  - Lernoux, Penny. In Banks We Trust. Garden City: Anchor Press., 1984 (Box 118)
  - Ambrose, Stephen E. Undaunted Courage. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1996 (Box 118)
  - Ornstein, Robert and Richard F. Thompson. The Amazing Brain. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1984 (Box 118)
  - Beard, Rick and Leslie Cohen Berlowitz (eds). Greenwich Village: Culture and Counterculture. New Brunswick: Rutgers University Press., 1993 (Box 118)
  - Alperovitz, Atomic Diplomacy: Hiroshima and Potsdam. London: Pluto Press., 1985 (Box 119)
  - Pipes, Richard. The Russian Revolution. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1991 (Box 119)
  - Richardson, Robert D. Emerson: The Mind on Fire. Berkeley: University of California Press., 1995 (Box 119)
  - Alperovitz, Gar. The Decision to Use the Atomic Bomb. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1995 (Box 119)
  - Sheehan, George. Getting Fit and Feeling Great. New York: Wings Books., 1983 (Box 119)
  - Homberger, Eric. Scenes from the Life of a City. New Haven: Yale University Press., 1994 (Box 119)
  - Rosenthal, M.L. Our Life in Poetry. New York: Persea Books., 1991 (Box 119)
  - Dwork, Deborah. Children with a Star. New Haven: Yale University Press., 1991 (Box 119)
  - Mellow, James R. Nathaniel Hawthorne in His Times. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1980 (Box 120)
  - Boyd, Brian. Vladimir Nabokov: The American Years. Princeton: Princeton University Press., 1991 (Box 120)
  - Pipes, Richard. Russian Under the Bolshevik Regime. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1993 (Box 120)
  - Knowlson, James. Damned to Fame: The Life of Samuel Beckett. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1996 (Box 120)
  - Rhodes, Richard. The Making of the Atomic Bomb. New York: Simon and Schuster., 1986 (Box 120)
  - Lopate, Phillip. Against Joie de Vivre. New York: Poseidon Press., 1989 (Box 120)
  - Sklar, Morty and Joseph Barbato (eds). Patchwork of Dreams: Voices from the Heart of New America. New York: The Spirit that Moves Us Press., 1996 (Box 120)
  - Augarde, Tony. The Oxford Guide to Word Games. Oxford: Oxford University Press., 1984 (Box 120)
  - Wyman, David S. The Abandonment of the Jews. New York: Pantheon Books., 1985 (Box 120)
  - Shapiro, Dani. Fugitive Blue. New York: Double Day., 1993 (Box 120)
  - The Monthly Review. Vol. 6. No. 3., 1954 (Box 120)
  - Balaban, John. The Hawk's Tale. San Diego: Gulliver Books., 1988 (Box 120)
  - Miller, Henry. Nights of Love and Laughter. New York: Signet Books, 1955 (Box 122)
  - Thoreau, Henry David. Walden and Other Writings. New York: Bantam Books., 1989 (Box 122)
  - Trumbo, Dalton. Johnny Got His Gun. New York: Bantam Books., 1989 (Box 122)
  - Dreiser, Theodore. Sister Carrie. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1958 (Box 122)
  - Berlin, Isaiah. The Hudgehog and the Fox. New York: Mentor Books., 1957 (Box 122)
  - Burroughs, William S. Naked Lunch. New York: Grove Press., 1966 (Box 122)
  - Arnold, Matthew. Four Essays on Life and Letters. New York: F.S. Crofts and Co., 1947 (Box 122)
  - Huxley, Thomas Henry. Selections from the Essays of T.H. Huxley. New York: F.S. Crofts and Co., 1948 (Box 122)
  - Bacon, Francis. Selected Essays of Francis Bacon. New York: F.S. Crofts and Co., 1948 (Box 122)
  - Conrad, Joseph. The Secret Agent. New York: Signet Classics., 1983 (Box 122)
  - Melville, Herman. Typee. New York: A Signet Classic., 1964 (Box 122)
  - Anderson, Sherwood. Winesburg, Ohio. New York: Penguin Books., 1946 (Box 122)
  - Crane, Milton (ed). 50 Great American Short Stories. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1959 (Box 122)
  - Greene, Theodore Meyer (ed). Kant Selections. New York: Charles Scribner's Sons., 1929 (Box 122)
  - Bellow, Saul. Dangling Man. New York: Signet Classics., 1944 (Box 122)
  - Twain, Mark. The Adventures of Tom Sawyer. Toronto: Bantam Classics., 1981 (Box 122)
  - James, Henry. The Turn of the Screw. New York: Signet Classics., 1962 (Box 122)
  - Delbanco, Nicholas. Old Scores. New York: Warner Books., 1997 (Box 122)
  - Ontario Review. No 40, 52, 54, 61, 65, 67, 1994-2008 (Box 122)
  - The Paris Review. Vol. 30 No. 109, 1988 (Box 122)
  - Daedalus. Vol. 141. No. 1, 2012 (Box 122)
  - Lewis, Anthony. Freedom for the Thought that We Hate. New York: Perseus Book., 2007 (Box 124)
  - Simons, Howard. Jewish Times. Boston: Houghton Mifflin Company., 1988 (Box 124)
  - Lewis, Anthony. Freedom for the Thought Thought That We Hate. New York: Basic Books., 2007 (Box 124)
  - Pawel, Ernst. The Nightmare of Reason. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1984 (Box 124)
  - Levy, Alan. The Wiesenthal File. Grand Rapids: William B. Eerdmans Publishing Company., 1993 (Box 124)
  - Maass, Joachim. Kleist: A Biography. New York: Farrar, Straus, Giroux., 1983 (Box 124)
  - Leitner, Isabella. The Big Lie. New York: Scholastic Inc., 1992 (Box 124)
  - Kaufman, Alan. Jew Boy. New York: Fromm International., 2000 (Box 124)
  - Willis, Ellen. Don't Think, Smile!. Boston: Beacon Press., 1999 (Box 124)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur M.. The Disuniting of America: Reflections on a Multicultural Society. New York: W.W. Norton and Co., 1992 (Box 124)
  - Baker, Jean-Claude and Chris Chase. Josephine. New York: Random House., 1993 (Box 124)
  - Gribbin, John. Forecasts, Famines and Freezes. New York: Walker and Company., 1976 (Box 124)
  - Cervantes, Miguel de and Edith Grossman (trans). Don Quixote. New York: Harper Collins., 2003 (Box 124)
  - Janvier, Thomas A. In Old New York. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1999 (Box 125)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir. Bend Sinister. New York: Time Incorporated., 1964 (Box 125)
  - Stendhal and Robert M. Adams (trans). Red and Black. New York: W.W. Norton and Company., 1969 (Box 125)
  - Johnson, Fenton. Scissors, Paper, Rock. New York: Pocket Books., 1993 (Box 125)
  - Coburn, Randy Sue. Remembering Jody. New York: Carroll and Graf Publishers, Inc., 1999 (Box 125)
  - Powers, Charles T. In the Memory of the Forest. New York: Scribner., 1997 (Box 125)
  - Farrell, James T. Gas-House McGinty. New York: The World Publishing Company., 1944 (Box 125)
  - Rosenfeld, Isaac. An Age of Enormity. New York: The World Publishing Company., 1962 (Box 125)
  - Cole, K.C. Sympathetic Vibrations. Toronto: Bantam Books., 1984 (Box 125)
  - Jacobus, Lee A. A World of Ideas. New York: St. Martin's Press., 1983 (Box 125)
  - Levin, Gail. Edward Hopper. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 1995 (Box 125)
  - Silverman, Kenneth. Lightning Man: The Accursed Life of Samuel F.B. Morse. New York: Alfred A. Knopf., 2003 (Box 125)
  - Bloom, Harold. The Western Canon. New York: Harcourt Brace and Company., 1994 (Box 125)